Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Hodge, Frederick Webb (Box 40-41)
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 18; postcard
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 18; postcard
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 22; postcard
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 25; postcard
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 May 11
    - To Boas, 1909 May 14
    - To Boas, 1909 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 June 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 14; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1910 May 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31
    - To Boas, 1910 June 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1911 May 12
    - To Boas, 1911 May 26
    - To Boas, 1911 May 29
    - To Boas, 1911 May 31
    - To Boas, 1911 May 31; telegram
    - To Boas, 1911 June 3
    - To Boas, 1911 June 6
    - To Boas, 1911 June 9
    - To Boas, 1911 June 24
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec.
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 6; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 June 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 13; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 May 13
    - To Boas, 1913 May 15
    - To Boas, 1913 May 17; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1913 June 18
    - To Boas, 1913 July 1
    - To Boas, 1913 July 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 July 22
    - To Boas, 1913 July 24
    - To Boas, 1913 July 30
    - To Boas, 1913 July 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec.; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 July 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 June 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 June 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 June 7
    - To Boas, 1915 June 16
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1916 June 19
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 2?; 1p.
    - (See Hrdlicka, A. to Hodge, F.W. Mar. 27, 1919), 1919 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1900 May 10; 2p.
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1900 May 14; 2p.
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1900 June 21; 1p.
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1900 Aug. 8; 1p.
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1915 Feb. 3
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1915 May 29; telegram
    - F.W. Hodge -- to H.A. Andrews, 1915 June 10
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1900 May 12; 1p.
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1900 July 30
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1900 Aug. 7
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1900 Aug. 7
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1902 Sept. 11
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1902 Sept. 27
    - H.A. Andrews -- to F.W. Hodge, 1905 Sept. 11
    - F.W.H. -- from C.M. Buchanan, 1913 Dec. 7
    - F.W.H. -- from Stewart Culin, 1899 June 3
    - F.W. Hodge -- from Robert Fletcher, 1899 June 5
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1911 Dec. 14
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1912 Feb. 5
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1912 Oct. 18
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1913 May 20
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1913 May 20
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1913 June 4
    - F.W. Hodge -- from L.J. Frachtenberg, 1913 June 20
    - F.W. Hodge -- to L.J. Frachtenberg, 1913 May 26
    - F.W. Hodge -- to L.J. Frachtenberg, 1913 June 11
    - F.W. Hodge -- to L.J. Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 8
    - F.W. Hodge -- to L.J. Frachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 13
    - F.W. Hodge -- from A.A. Goldenweiser, 1914 Aug. 3
    - F.W. Hodge -- to A.A. Goldenweiser, 1914 Aug. 5
    - F.W. Hodge -- to E.W. Hawkes, 1913 Dec. 10
    - F.W. Hodge -- from A.L. Kroeber, 1907 Oct. 29
    - F.W. Hodge -- from M.A. Miner, 1908 Dec. 9
    - F.W.H. -- from C.E. Myers, 1901 Oct. 31
    - F.W.H. -- from New Era Printing Co., 1901 Sep. 25
    - F.W. Hodge -- from F.S. Nichols, 1917 Oct. 31 andNov. 1
    - F.W.H. -- to Elsie Clewes Parsons, 1919 June 27
    - F.W. Hodge -- from P.B. Pierce, 1900 Oct. 8
    - F.W.H. -- to G.P.Putnam's Sons, 1899 Feb.7; 1p.
    - F.W.H. -- from G.P.Putnam's Sons, 1899 Dec. 19
    - F.W. Hodge -- from E. Sapir, 1917 Apr. 19
    - F.W. Hodge -- to Harlan I. Smith, 1914 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - F.W. Hodge -- from Edith Elmer Wood, 1903 Feb. 28
  - Hodges, Charles (Box 41)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
  - Hodges, N.D.C. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1889 Jan.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1889 Jan. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 May 2
    - To Boas, ? May 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - N.D.C. Hodges -- from S.C. Derby, 1887 June 7
  - Hodgson, E. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept.; card
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec.; 1p.
  - Hoebel, A. (Box 41)
    - To Boas, 1933 July 6; 2p.
  - Hoebel, E. Adamson (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 2; 1p.
  - Hoechester, Emil (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p.
  - Hoen, A., & Co. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 9; 1p.
  - Hofe, von (Box 41)
    - Hofe, von -- from W. Lehmann, 1933 Aug. 30
    - (Enc. with Schneider, K., Sept. 6, 1933)
    - Hofe, von -- to K. Schneider, 1933 Sept. 1; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Schneider, K., Sept. 6, 1933)
  - Hoffman, B.F. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 23; telegram
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 25; telegram
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Hoffman, Conrad Jr. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Hoffman, Curt (Box 41)
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Hoffman, E. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 4; 2p.
  - Hoffman, Frederick L. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 7; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - (Enc: Anthropometric measurements of male Maricopa...Indians of Arizona, Anthropometric measurements of female Maricopa...Indians of Arizona, 1920. 1920.)
  - Hoffman, Malvina (Box 41)
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 17; 1p.
  - Hoffman, R.J. (Box 41)
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 30; 1p.
  - Hoffman, W.H. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 12; 2p.
  - Hoffman, W.J. (Box 41)
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - Hoffman, International UMCA (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p.
  - Hoffmann, G. Karl, 1932 Oct; 7p. (Box 41)
  - Hoffmann-Krayer, E. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 18; 3p.
  - Hofman, Bernhard (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 2; 1p.
  - Hofmann, Julius (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 8; 1p.
  - Hognera, E. (Box 41)
    - To Boas, 1917 June 24
  - Hohlfeld, A.R. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p.
  - Hohlfeld, A.R. -- (cont'd) (Box 41)
    - From Boas
    - See Boas, F. to Francke, K. Nov. 28,1905, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 end; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 1; 1p.
  - Hoijer, Harry L. (Box 41)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Comm. on Native American Languages...Hoijer...Apr. 29, 1940), 1940 May 6; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. To Comm. on Native American Languages, May 31, 1940
    - See Boas, F. to Bloomfield, L., July 31, 1940
    - See Boas, F. to Swadesh, M. Feb.6, 1941, 1941 July 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 19; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - H. Hoijer -- from B.C. Edel
      - See Edel, B.C. to Cowan, J.M., Dec. 30,1942
      - See Edel, B.C. to Bloomfiels, L., Jan.6,1943
  - Hoisington, Mrs. F.R. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 1; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - Mrs. F.R. Hoisington -- from F.W. Wakeman, 1912 June 24
  - Hoke, S.W. (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 17
  - Hoke, Travis (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 7; 1p.
  - Holbrook, H. (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - (Enc. originally with Barnes, H.E., July 8, 1918)
  - Holbrooks (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1900 Oct. 4
  - Holcombe, Arthur N. (Box 42)
    - A.N. Holcombe -- to C.R. Miller, 1939 July 9; telegram
  - Holden, A.H. (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 30
  - Holland, W.J. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 23; 2p.
  - Holleben (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 28
  - Hollick, Arthur (Box 42)
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1897 Dec. 8
  - Hollick, C.A. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7; 2p.
  - Holliday, C. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 2
  - Hollingworth, H.L. (Box 42)
    - See Poffenberger, A.T., Oct. 18, 1939.
  - Holly, Alonzo P. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 19; 1p.
  - Holmes, John H. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 3; telegr
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 28; 1p.
  - Holmes, W.H. (Box 42)
    - From Boas, 1893 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Mar. 5; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 May 9; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1903 June 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 June 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 June 2; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1903 June 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 July 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 July 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 11
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 28; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 2; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 25; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 15; 14p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 June 31
    - From Boas, 1904 July 7
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1905 May 24
    - From Boas, 1905 May 24
    - From Boas, 1905 May 24
    - From Boas, 1905 May 27
    - From Boas, 1905 June 1
    - From Boas, 1905 June 5
    - From Boas, 1905 June 14
    - From Boas, 1905 June 15
    - From Boas, 1905 June 15
    - From Boas, 1905 June 15
    - From Boas, 1905 June 15
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 19
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 11
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 June 4
    - From Boas, 1906 June 5
    - From Boas, 1906 June 13
    - From Boas, 1906 June 13
    - From Boas, 1906 July 12
    - From Boas, 1906 July 12
    - From Boas, 1906 July 14
    - From Boas, 1906 July 16
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 3
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 May 4
    - From Boas, 1907 May 7
    - From Boas, 1907 May 10
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21
    - From Boas, 1907 May 24
    - From Boas, 1907 May 24
    - From Boas, 1907 May 27
    - From Boas, 1907 May 27
    - From Boas, 1907 June 1
    - From Boas, 1907 June 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept.7
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 26; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 June 22
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - (See Boas, F. to Gordon, G.B. May 22, 1916), 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8, 1916), 1918 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Cadman, S.P., May 29, 1929
    - To Boas, 1886
    - (See Holmes, W.H. Aug.5, 1886), 1886 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Aug. 6; 3p.